const quizQuestions2en = [{
    question:"Coated electrodes must be stored ...",
    answers: ["free of any packaging as they are developed to work in the field;",
    "in a controlled environment at high temperatures;",
    "in a dry environment, with temperature depending on their type, in accordance with the manufacturer's instructions;",
    "in an oven, with a temperature never exceeding 100 °C so as not to dry them too much."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"If a current higher than that specified by the manufacturer is used for a coated electrode, it may happen that it will ...",
    answers: ["fuse faster and improve the performance of the welder;",
    "damage the electrode coating and the weld may not pass a quality control;",
    "burn the welding power source;",
    "burn the welder's hand when changing the electrode."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Which of the following parameters is regulated at the power source in the case of welding with coated electrode?",
    answers: ["Welding current.",
    "Arc voltage.",
    "Arc length.",
    "Arc power."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"The component part of a welding machine that changes AC to DC is called:",
    answers: ["Resistor;",
    "Transformer;",
    "Rectifier;",
    "Inductor."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Direct current (DC) is the electrical current that ...",
    answers: ["flows through a conductor in one direction only;",
    "generates heat in a conductor;",
    "does not generates heat in a conductor;",
    "flows through a conductor from left to right."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Alternating current (AC) is the current that ...",
    answers: ["suddenly changes its value;",
    "can be turned on and off frequently;",
    "flows through a conductor, now in one direction, now in the opposite direction, with a determined frequency;",
    "fluctuates between two value levels without changing its direction."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"The outlet of the public network (electric socket) provides ...",
    answers: ["constant current, as the available voltage (127 V, 220 V or other) does not change its value;",
    "constant current, as it does not vary, unless there is a change in resistance in the electrical circuit;",
    "alternating current, with a pre-set polarity;",
    "alternating current."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How are you going to convince the customer that for MMA welding (SMAW) a direct current power source is better than a welding transformer?",
    answers: ["It always consumes less energy.",
    "It has a longer service life.",
    "It allows the use of coated electrodes of all types, developed for both direct current and alternating current.",
    "It allows welding in all positions."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How should the welder handle the electrodes to keep them free from contaminants (dirt, moisture, ...) and to prevent electrodes of different types from mixing with each other?",
    answers: ["Keep the electrodes, that will not be used immediately, in its packaging.",
    "Always remove the electrodes from the packaging one at a time.",
    "Never remove more than 10 electrodes from the package at a time.",
    "Before returning the electrodes in their packaging, always clean them with a damp cloth."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"What are you going to suggest to the customer, to weld closer to the power source using shorter welding cables or to use longer cables to increase the range?",
    answers: ["It is always best not to move the power source and, if necessary, increase the length of welding cables.",
    "Even if it is a light and easy to move power source (e.g., inverter type), it is recommended to use the power cable as short as possible to reduce energy losses in it (heating by the Joule effect).",
    "It is recommended to keep the welding cables as short as possible to reduce energy losses in them (heating by the Joule effect).",
    "The welding cables can be of any length, as the power source always maintains the preset current value."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"What type of electrode is used for TIG welding (GTAW)?",
    answers: ["Consumable.",
    "Non consumable.",
    "Flux coated electrode.",
    "Made of titanium."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How should you argue to convince a customer to buy a power source for welding with coated electrodes?",
    answers: ["It will permit to weld steel and steel with aluminium.",
    "It is a versatile and inexpensive welding process.",
    "Good use of consumables (almost no loss of electrodes).",
    "The customer will not need any prior training to be able to weld well."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How should you argue to convince a customer to buy a power source for welding with coated electrodes?",
    answers: ["There are many electrodes available on the market even for welding steel with aluminium.",
    "Weld quality is better than in TIG (GTAW) welding.",
    "This process of joining the materials is fast and gives a good quality.",
    "There is no need to use PPE."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How should you argue to convince a customer to buy a power source for welding with coated electrodes?",
    answers: ["Weld quality is better than in TIG (GTAW) welding.",
    "The customer will not need any prior training to be able to weld well.",
    "There is no need to use PPE.",
    "This welding process can fix many metallic pieces in the house (gate, gardening tools, chairs and others)."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How should you argue to convince a customer to buy a power source for welding with coated electrodes?",
    answers: ["There are many electrodes available on the market.",
    "Weld quality is better than in TIG (GTAW) welding.",
    "The customer will not need any prior training to be able to weld well.",
    "There is no need to use PPE."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"One of the gases used in MIG welding is:",
    answers: ["Acetylene.",
    "Butane.",
    "Argon.",
    "CO"],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Using one disadvantage of MMA/SMAW welding, how will you convince the customer to buy more coated electrodes of different diameters?",
    answers: ["It is hard to weld in overhead position, thus, it is good to use thicker electrodes to finish weld as fast as possible.",
    "When welding in a vertical position, the weld pool has a tendency to run down. In this case it is better to use thicker electrodes to cool the liquid metal.",
    "When welding in a flat position, the size of the weld pool must be larger (otherwise the electrode will stick to the part). In this case it is better to use thinner electrodes, as they offer higher melting rates.",
    "For each reduction in plate thickness by 1 - 2 mm, an electrode with every time smaller diameter must be used."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"How are you going to convince the customer to buy more coated electrodes?",
    answers: ["To finish a job there are always 1 or 2 electrodes missing.",
    "Electrodes are cheap and it is worth buying more to have a reserve in case you urgently need them.",
    "It is very easy to store coated electrodes as the coating protects their soul from rust.",
    "The coated electrodes do not lose their characteristics even after 2 - 3 years of storage."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"What welding cable would you suggest to your customer?",
    answers: ["The thinnest, as it is more flexible and cheaper.",
    "The thickest, because although the welding current value is not known, it would be working in favour of safety.",
    "The thinnest on the ground cable and the thickest on the electrode holder, as this second conducts more current.",
    "It doesn't matter if the cable is thin or thick, the most important is to have the best insulation."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"The customer searches for a welding cable. What factor will you take into account when choosing the minimum section of the welding cable? (It is just one of the factors to be taken into account)",
    answers: ["Welding current value.",
    "No-load voltage of the welding power source.",
    "Type of the welding process (e.g., MMA or MIG/MAG).",
    "Working conditions (inside the workshop or in the field)."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"The customer searches for a welding cable. What factor will you take into account when choosing the minimum section of the welding cable? (It is just one of the factors to be taken into account)",
    answers: ["Distance from the power source to the welding place.",
    "No-load voltage of the welding power source.",
    "Type of the welding process (e.g., MMA or MIG/MAG).",
    "Working conditions (inside the workshop or in the field)."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"The customer searches for a welding cable. What factor will you take into account when choosing the minimum section of the welding cable? (It is just one of the factors to be taken into account)",
    answers: ["Duty cycle: 20%, 40%, 60%, ...",
    "No-load voltage of the welding power source.",
    "Type of the welding process (e.g., MMA or MIG/MAG).",
    "Working conditions (inside the workshop or in the field)."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Why, in the case of welding with coated electrodes, does the customer usually buy the ground cable shorter than the cable for the electrode holder?",
    answers: ["Because, if needed, it is easier to add the length of the ground cable than the cable of the electrode holder;",
    "Because, it is not necessary to connect the ground cable to the piece, its end can be simply grounded;",
    "The useful life of ground cables is longer, so there is always a certain amount of cable left over in the company;",
    "The ground cable can be shorter, as the metal structure itself can serve as an extension of the ground cable."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Which thermal cutting process is not suitable for cutting stainless steel?",
    answers: ["Oxy-gas cutting.",
    "Plasma cutting.",
    "Laser cutting.",
    "Plasma under water cutting."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Oxy-fuel cutting is restricted to:",
    answers: ["Cast iron group;",
    "Stainless steel group;",
    "Group of ferrous metals;",
    "Group of non-ferrous metals."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Oxyfuel cutting can be used to cut:",
    answers: ["carbon steels;",
    "all types of metals, without any special technique application;",
    "aluminium;",
    "stainless steels without any special technique application."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Which of these abbreviations does NOT refer to a welding process?",
    answers: ["MIG.",
    "TIG.",
    "MAG.",
    "TOC."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0 "
    },
     {
    question:"Which single-phase welding machine will consume more current from the public network, that of the 380 V or 220 V supply voltage?",
    answers: ["The 380 V one, because the higher the voltage, the higher the current.",
    "The 220 V one, because the lower the supply voltage, the higher the current consumption must be to ensure the same electrical power of the machine.",
    "The 220 V one, because the lower the supply voltage, the higher the current consumption must be, although this machine will be heated more than the 380 V one.",
    "The current consumption is the same, otherwise the output current (welding current) will be different as well."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0 "},
    {
    question:"Which of these materials has the highest electrical conductivity (conducts electricity better)?",
    answers: ["Water.",
    "Copper.",
    "Steel.",
    "Bakelite."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these materials has the lowest electrical conductivity (has high electrical resistance)?",
    answers: ["Water.",
    "Copper.",
    "Steel.",
    "Bakelite."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these materials has the worst thermal conductivity (best thermal insulation)?",
    answers: ["Copper.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Steel.",
    "Bakelite."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these materials has the highest thermal conductivity (conducts heat better)?",
    answers: ["Stainless steel.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Carbon steel.",
    "Bakelite."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of the following metals is non-ferrous?",
    answers: ["Steel.",
    "Cast iron.",
    "Copper.",
    "Malleable Iron."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"The most common ferrous metals are:",
    answers: ["aluminium and magnesium;",
    "copper and brass;",
    "zinc and lead;",
    "carbon steel and cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"How the material density is expressed?",
    answers: ["Mass per unit volume.",
    "Mass per square centimetre.",
    "Mass per square millimetre.",
    "Mass per square meter."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of the following materials has the highest mechanical strength?",
    answers: ["Copper.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Steel.",
    "Bakelite."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of the materials below has the lowest mechanical strength?",
    answers: ["Copper.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Steel.",
    "Lead."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of the materials below has the lowest mechanical strength?",
    answers: ["Copper.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Steel.",
    "Cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What properties has copper compared to steel?",
    answers: ["Higher thermal conductivity.",
    "Smaller density (lighter).",
    "Higher melting point.",
    "Lower electrical conductivity."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What properties has copper compared to steel?",
    answers: ["Higher electrical conductivity.",
    "Smaller density (lighter).",
    "Higher melting point.",
    "Lower thermal conductivity."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which material is made of a matrix and reinforcer that together have better properties than the individual materials?",
    answers: ["Super alloy.",
    "Ceramic.",
    "Polymer.",
    "Composite."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these materials has the highest thermal conductivity (conducts heat better)?",
    answers: ["Stainless steel.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Carbon steel.",
    "Copper."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which material has lowest thermal conductivity (conducts heat worse)?",
    answers: ["Stainless steel.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Carbon steel.",
    "Copper."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What tools shall be used when handling stainless steel?",
    answers: ["any tool can be used (maid of bronze, high strength steel, aluminium, ...) as long as it is new;",
    "any tool can be used (maid of bronze, high strength steel, aluminium, ...) as long as it is clean;",
    "any tool can be used (maid of bronze, high strength steel, aluminium, ...), provided it was always used for stainless steels only;",
    "only stainless steel tools and reserved for stainless steel only."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What type of brushes shall be used for cleaning of joint preparations in stainless steels?",
    answers: ["any type of wire brush as long as it is new;",
    "any type of wire brush as long as it is clean;",
    "any type of wire brush, provided it was always used for stainless steels only;",
    "only stainless steel brushes, even used."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What is the major element in carbon steel?",
    answers: ["Iron.",
    "Nickel.",
    "Carbon.",
    "Chromium."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"A farmer needs to weld/repair some stainless steel parts on agricultural machinery. He knows how to weld with coated electrodes. Would you suggest to him:",
    answers: ["to buy new parts, as there is no way to weld stainless steel parts in the field;",
    "to buy a TIG (GTAW) machine, as this process offers the best weld quality;",
    "to buy a MIG/MAG (GMAW) machine, as this process offers the highest production (deposition rate);",
    "to buy an MMA machine (SMAW) and covered electrodes for stainless steel."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, is there covered electrodes for welding aluminium?",
    answers: ["Yes!",
    "No!",
    "No, but electrodes for stainless steels can be used for welding aluminium.",
    "No, but electrodes with a white coating can also be used to weld aluminium."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Mercury is:",
    answers: ["a non-metal;",
    "a metal; ",
    "a natural alloy;",
    "a non-metal that is always in a liquid state."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of the following metals remains in liquid form under normal conditions?",
    answers: ["Radium.",
    "Zinc.",
    "Mercury.",
    "Uranium."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"1"},
    {
    question:"The force is measured in:",
    answers: ["Pa;",
    "N.m;",
    "N/m;",
    "N."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"Express 33% as a decimal:",
    answers: ["3,3;",
    "0,033;",
    "0,33;",
    "33."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"Express 42% as a decimal:",
    answers: ["4,2;",
    "0,042;",
    "0,42;",
    "42."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"Express 3% as a decimal:",
    answers: ["0,3;",
    "0,003;",
    "0,03;",
    "3."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"Express 1% as a decimal:",
    answers: ["0,1;",
    "0,001;",
    "0,01;",
    "1."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"40 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["100;",
    "150;",
    "160;",
    "200."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"20 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["50;",
    "60;",
    "80;",
    "100."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"30 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["90;",
    "100;",
    "120;",
    "150."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"60 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["120;",
    "180;",
    "240;",
    "300."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"70 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["140;",
    "210;",
    "280;",
    "350."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"80 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["160;",
    "240;",
    "320;",
    "400."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"90 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["180;",
    "240;",
    "360;",
    "450."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"25 is 25% of:",
    answers: ["75;",
    "80;",
    "100;",
    "125."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"Calculate the total amount of sheet steel required to construct an enclosed cubic tank of 1 m x 1 m x 1 m:",
    answers: ["4 m²;",
    "5 m²;",
    "6 m²;",
    "8 m²."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"A welder/operator should protect himself against radiation by using:",
    answers: ["a welding curtain;",
    "auto-darkening glasses;",
    "ear protectors;",
    "proper clothing and a welder’s mask with adequate filters."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Care must be taken with ultraviolet rays from the welding arc, as they can cause:",
    answers: ["Skin and eye burns;",
    "Equipment damage;",
    "Malaise;",
    "Excessive heating."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What safety equipment should be used in welding?",
    answers: ["Apron, shoes, sunglasses, leather gloves.",
    "Apron, shoes, welding mask or sunglasses for oxygas welding, gloves and leather leggings.",
    "Apron, shoes, welding mask, gloves and leather leggings.",
    "Apron, shoes, safety glasses, leather gloves and leggings (only for welding with covered electrodes)."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3What safety equipment should be used in welding?"
    },
    {
    question:"Which scale numbers for a welding filter according to EN 169 gives the darkest shade?",
    answers: ["8",
    "10",
    "12",
    "14"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"According to the International System of Units, volume is measured in:",
    answers: ["l (litre);",
    "m3 (cubic metre);",
    "gallon;",
    "quart;"],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What must be done immediately after cylinders are unloaded?",
    answers: ["Chain them up.",
    "Check their valves for leaks.",
    "Check for proper labelling on them.",
    "Connect a gauge and check the pressure level."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Acetone can be discharged unless acetylene cylinders are stored in what position?",
    answers: ["Inclined.",
    "Vertical.",
    "Stacked.",
    "Horizontal."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What is the main purpose of the welding mask?",
    answers: ["Ensure comfort to the welder.",
    "Protect the welder from radiation emitted by the welding arc.",
    "Protect the welder against harmful gases.",
    "Protect the welder's head against mechanical shocks."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"The acronym PPE corresponds to which item?",
    answers: ["Protection of People and Equipment.",
    "Protection of Person and Equipment.",
    "Personal Protective Equipment.",
    "Philosophy of Protection and Equipment."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"It is one of the suitable eye protection equipment for arc welding stations:",
    answers: ["a shield with a protective filter lens;",
    "sunglasses;",
    "sunglasses (for other workers);",
    "non-transparent protective curtains."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"It is one of the suitable eye protection equipment for arc welding stations:",
    answers: ["sunglasses;",
    "sunglasses (for other workers);",
    "non-transparent protective curtains;",
    "transparent welding protective curtains."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"You sold a welding power source for the price of $500,00. The purchase cost for your shop was 4/5 of the selling price. What is the profit (not taking into account other expenses)?",
    answers: ["$50,00",
    "$100,00",
    "$150,00",
    "$200,00"],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"One of your customers is going to make three welds measuring 72 cm, 31 cm and 89 cm. What will be the total length of the welds?",
    answers: ["1 m and 92 cm.",
    "182 cm.",
    "0,192 m.",
    "2 m and 02 cm."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"When lifting a gas cylinder, you should:",
    answers: ["always lift from the bottom;",
    "keep your legs straight;",
    "lift using your back;",
    "lift with your legs."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"When lifting a gas cylinder, you should:",
    answers: ["always lift from the bottom;",
    "keep your legs straight;",
    "lift using your back;",
    "get help, if possible."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"When lifting a gas cylinder, you should:",
    answers: ["always lift from the bottom;",
    "keep your legs straight;",
    "lift using your back;",
    "remove any slip hazards from your path."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Suitable clothing material for welders is:",
    answers: ["Traditional cotton.",
    "Wool.",
    "Leather.",
    "65% cotton, 35% polyester."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Suitable clothing material for welders is:",
    answers: ["Traditional cotton.",
    "Wool.",
    "Chemically treated (flame-resistant) cotton.",
    "65% cotton, 35% polyester."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Why are cylinder caps kept in place when the cylinder is not in use? ",
    answers: ["So, no dust gets into the valve.",
    "To protect the valve.",
    "To hook a crane to for lifting.",
    "So, the valves cannot be opened."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What is allowed when handling gas cylinders used in welding?",
    answers: ["Stop consumption just before zero in order to avoid contamination of the system.",
    "Consume all the gas in the cylinder to avoid losses.",
    "Handle two cylinders at a time.",
    "Keep them as close to the welding site as possible to avoid gas losses."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What is allowed when handling gas cylinders used in welding?",
    answers: ["Physical contact of the cylinder with an electrical circuit.",
    "Prolonged exposure to the sun.",
    "Keep them at least 5 m away from any heat source.",
    "Displace them lying down by rolling."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What is allowed when handling gas cylinders used in welding?",
    answers: ["Keep them as close to the welding site as possible to avoid gas losses.",
    "Prolonged exposure to the sun.",
    "Keep them as close to the welding location as possible to avoid pressure reduction.",
    "Displace them by rolling while maintaining in vertical position."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What is allowed when handling gas cylinders used in welding?",
    answers: ["Transport two cylinders on an appropriate cart.",
    "Prolonged exposure to the sun.",
    "Keep them as close to the welding location as possible to avoid pressure reduction.",
    "Handle two cylinders at a time."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"}
];